hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Hurry!
Right...
We're close!
There are two enemies left...
There are three of us...
It's three against two.
We might be able to do it with
one more contact if we do it well.
All right! All right!
Let's do it!
No! It's four against two!
Okay, okay! I'm sorry.
Counting Akamaru,
it's four against two!
Let's finish it quickly with
our new technique next!
Hey, hey. If necessary,
I'll do an awesome Shadow Clone,
so it'll be okay!
That's reassuring...
But my strategy comes first. Got it?
Y-Yeah...
For that purpose,
we have to catch up
before the sun sets at any cost.
I know. Full throttle!
The sun's starting to set...
Neither Jirobo nor
Kidomaru have come.
It seems they're having
a hard time.
It doesn't matter...
More important is Orochimaru-sama.
We've only completed one-third
of the journey in half a day...
They all have Curse Marks, huh...
No questions asked, huh?
This is gonna be different
than that time before
with your surprise attack...
Too much interference...
Yeah, this is bad...
We don't know whether
we'll make it in time at this rate!
Damn! We still can't catch up...
No, this is good enough.
We'll maintain this distance
and continue the pursuit...
Wh-What do you mean?
I mean we're delaying
the attack until dawn breaks.
Get real!
We can't afford such leisure!
That's right! Besides if we're going
to attack anyway,
isn't it more advantageous
to use the darkness and attack?!
For us the darkness works
to our advantage
only the moment
we launch the attack.
It'd be close to impossible
to grab Sasuke,
get away from them and escape
to a safe location
in just that one moment.
If we couldn't get Sasuke
back in that one moment,
they'd probably just focus
on guarding the coffin.
If that happens we wouldn't stand
a chance in the darkness.
On the contrary,
for the part where they wouldn't
have to move needlessly,
suddenly they'd get the advantage.
It'd be a different story
if we had Neji's Byakugan but...
Hey, come on.
Aren't you forgetting Akamaru's nose
and mine as well??
I was sure to include your senses
of smell in the calculations!
Even so, up ahead they have
the geographical advantage.
Plus...
if I can't use my Jutsu
it'll be no use.
Even if I seal off their movements
with Shadow Possession Jutsu...
the effect would be reduced to half
if clouds were to cover the moon.
It's a drag but there are too many
dangers and uncertain elements.
But!
Got it!
Naruto?
You're the leader...
I'll follow your instructions, Shikamaru!
Right. I'm counting on you!
Get Back
The Container That Didn't
Make It In Time
~
Hey, Tayuya!
Will we really make it in time?
I was just told to deliver
Sasuke-sama by tomorrow.
By tomorrow, huh?
I can't say that we have
lots of time to spare
but I guess we'll make it in time.
I hope so.
Orochimaru-sama...
Sasuke...
No Sasuke-kun... yet?
He's running out of time...
He can't go on any longer.
Orochimaru-sama...
Several bodies have been
prepared for you!
And... you could even use me
if necessary...
It has to be Sasuke-kun...
How long do you think I've waited?
It's a matter of urgency!
The Third Hokage's Jutsu...
His curse was stronger
than expected!
Take this! Sealing Jutsu!
Reaper Death Seal!
Wh-What's this sensation?
Seal!
My arm...
If you don't "reanimate" right now,
you'll lose everything!
Is that what you want?!
Lose everything...
I've selected and prepared
proficient bodies for you.
Please leave it to me! Also...
I'll handle the recovery
of Sasuke-kun as well.
Shall I use Kimimaro?
Damn you...
Third Hokage!
Seal
Release!
Listen well everyone!
I shall release you from this prison...
However, it'll only
be one of you!
Now all that's left is to
wake up Kimimaro-kun, huh?
Just as I thought...
I wasn't summoned this time either.
Kabuto-sensei, I...
Take care of your body.
Your role is now finished.
It's not Sound Ninja Five now,
Kimimaro-kun...
I... still haven't...
Your replacement has
already been found.
He possesses power equal
to your "Earth" Curse Mark.
He has been given
the "Heaven" Curse Mark.
Additionally, he even
has the Kekkei Genkai.
Wonder who's stronger...
What's the matter?
Don't get too excited.
Kabuto-sensei...
M-My life, how much do I have left?
You shouldn't talk anymore...
P-People... People are born
with some kind of meaning...
Since people are born
there must be some kind
of important calling.
Recently I've started thinking so...
That the meaning for being born...
For people finding the meaning is...
the only freedom God has given.
I understand what you want to say.
Indeed, Orochimaru-sama
is now suffering.
It's an unprecedented
difficult situation
but I'll mince no words.
What can you do now?
You've now lost your value
as a "vessel."
A new vessel is heading this way.
Well...
At this point in time
it's too late but...
Okay! You said you were going
to let one person out of here.
You're going to keep
your promise.
What're you doing?
Open the door now!
What? There was another one?
Hurry up and...
No... I...
I'll be eaten here right now...
I'll let you out of here...
And I shall grant you
just one wish.
My clan that was captured
for your experiments.
Please release them.
Sure. Consider it done.
You don't have to worry.
Your strong will is going to remain
as Residual Aura inside me.
It's not like you'll lose everything.
Now then your flesh is mine...
With this Orochimaru-sama's body
will once again
be unable to reanimate
for several years.
However, there is the next time.
I-Indeed...
my body no longer has value
as a vessel for Reanimation Jutsu.
It will now be difficult for me
who has lost everything...
to find my own calling.
I've finally understood that...
Even if it's not me,
I'll bring in the new "vessel"
even if it costs me my life.
That's my repayment to
Orochimaru-sama...
That's the only redemption
for me for being worthless...
Hold on a minute!
Are we almost there?
No... It should still take a while.
More importantly...
What were those idiots
Jirobo and Kidomaru doing?!
We caught up!
All right! I'll take care of
this nice and quick!
R-Right away?!
Eat this!
Multiple Fists Barrage!
Chakra in his palm...?!
Shadow Clone Transformation, eh?
Rasengan!
N-No way... His hands now...?!
There's no point if
I catch you before you do it!
— Now, Kiba!
— Tunneling Fang!
This was also a Shadow Clone?!
Luring Sakon into alignment with me...
and aiming at me from the start?!
You think you succeeded
just with that?!
Damn!
I've been nailed.
Shadow Possession Jutsu succeeded!
A diversion...
He's coming!
Tayuya! What're you doing
idling away?!
N-No!
Why do you move forward?!
I can't dodge!
Here you go!
Nice! Kiba, Shikamaru!
Shikamaru! Let's get out of here!
Yeah!
Punks...!
You scum... Messing around with us.
They were full of openings
just as I thought.
Having too much ability individually
is also a problem...
It went well.
Yeah, it went just as calculated!
Just in terms of teamwork
ours was way better than theirs.
I won't let you get away!
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
Damn it! To come this far
and have another one appear!
On top of that, there's something out
of the ordinary about this guy.
What's this bloodcurdling feeling
on my back?
Indeed, we are even on numbers
two against two.
But this...
I'm sorry, Naruto.
He's my miscalculation.
Next episode:
"Mistake! A New Enemy."